shopterrain.com 2018-01-09

# Help + Info Privacy + Security at Terrain

_**This Policy**_  
Thank you for shopping at shopterrain.com. This privacy and security policy (“Policy”) outlines the information we collect about you, how we use the information and the choices you have to review, modify, and/or restrict our usage of this information. 

_**Collected Information**_  
Shopterrain.com collects customer information for a variety of reasons, including as part of our ongoing efforts to provide superior customer service, to improve our customers' shopping experience, and to communicate with our customers about our products, services and promotions, including those that we believe may be of particular interest to you based on information we have collected. We collect personal information such as your name, financial information, telephone number, e-mail and postal address (“Personal Information”) that you provide to us when you save your information with us or when you participate in a sweepstakes, promotion or survey. We use this information to process any transaction, inquiry or promotion that you initiate with us. In addition, we maintain a record of your product interests, purchases and whatever else might enable us or our business partners to enhance and personalize your shopping experience on this or other websites and to provide you with offers, promotions or information that we believe may be of interest to you. We also monitor use of the Website and traffic patterns to improve the Website design and the products and services we offer as well as to determine what offers, promotions or information to send to you. 

_**Business Partners**_  
We contract with outside services to help us and our business partners better understand your use of shopterrain.com. These outside services may use cookies or other technologies to collect various kinds of information for us and our business partners related to your use of shopterrain.com, so that we and our business partners may continue to refine and improve this and other sites for our customers. We do not allow these parties to collect any credit card, user name or password information. These services are contractually required to maintain all the information collected for us in conformance with this Policy. As a visitor to shopterrain.com, you may "opt-out" of these types of collection of data. To learn more about your options you can[ click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). “Cookies” are bits of information that are automatically stored on your computer. If you do not want to have cookies on your system, you can set your browser to disable them. 

We or our partners may use Flash Cookies (also known as Local Stored Objects) or other similar technologies. A Flash cookie is a small data file placed on a computer using Adobe Flash or similar technology that may be built into your computer or downloaded or installed by you to your computer. We use these technologies to personalize and enhance your online experience, facilitate processes, personalize and store your settings. Flash cookies may help our website visitors to, for example, set volume preference associated with a video experience, play games and perform surveys. They help us improve our sites by measuring which areas are of greatest interest to customers. They may be recognized by other sites or by our marketing or business partners. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies and the cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. [Click here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html) to learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies. If you disable Flash cookies or other similar technologies, please be aware that you may not have access to certain features and services that make your online experience more efficient and enjoyable. 

We also use other methods of automatic collection to determine information about visitors to our website, including the IP address, browser, language preferences, and computer identification numbers. We use the information obtained using these tools to provide better customer service, enhance our product offerings, and detect potential misuse or fraud. 

_**Our Email List**_  
We offer those who sign up for our email list advanced notice of sales, new merchandise, store openings and other terrain news. If you would like to unsubscribe from our email list, contact us. We will remove your name from our email list reasonably soon. Please recognize that you may receive another email before we are able to remove you. 

_**Secure Shopping**_  
Sensitive personal information contained in orders placed on the Website is encrypted using 128-bit secure sockets layer (SSL) technology.* In order for SSL security to work, you must use an SSL enabled browser. *Secure Socket Layer (SSL) is a technology used by vendors to ensure the security of online business. It negotiates and employs the essential functions of mutual authentication, data encryption and data integrity for secure transactions.  
Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect you Personal Information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control; (b) the security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through the Website cannot be guaranteed; (c) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party; and (d) WHEN YOU TRANSFER ANY INFORMATION TO US, YOU DO SO AT YOUR OWN RISK. 

If you still have concerns about ordering electronically, feel free to call 877-5TERRAIN and place your order over the phone. Have the 6-character style code (ex. M411111), size, and color ready for each item you wish to order.   
Please note that e-mail is not encrypted and is not considered a secure means of transmitting credit card numbers. We will never ask for sensitive Personal Information via e-mail. 

*Secure Socket Layer (SSL) is a technology used by vendors to ensure the security of online business. It negotiates and employs the essential functions of mutual authentication, data encryption and data integrity for secure transactions. 

_**Policy Changes**_

Shopterrain.com may periodically update this Privacy & Security Policy for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed. Any changes made will be posted here. By visiting our website you agree to accept any changes made to this policy. The shopterrain.com Privacy & Security Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you on our website.

Feel free to contact us with any questions about our Privacy & Security Policy. 

_**Email**_  
service@shopterrain.com  
Phone  
877-5TERRAIN 

_**Mail**_  
terrain at Styer's  
755 Brackbill Road  
Gap, PA 17527  
Attn: Customer Service  
Policy effective date: October 8, 2012
